Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
I wonder if it's okay to have it.
ah?
So this is the second meeting without Mr. Sakuma... how's it going?
How's it going, everyone?
Last time we had a bit of a long meeting without Sakuma.
And when I told him it was fun, he sulked a little, like I'd suggested it.
The TV demon was sulking, so let's all have fun.
Let's have some fun together!
I'm sure you've seen it on TV before, but I've never done it before.
I've never done it before.
It's difficult and competitive.
I've failed in a competition... in that show with Oriji... yes, he was a tawashi, right?
I was a young comedian, so I had to make a reaction that I didn't want to do it, that I was scared.
I still remember that moment.
I knew then, didn't I? Youtube, how you looked when you were in the class in college...
He said he was making a face like he did when he was in a class in college and he was making a face like he'd reached his limit.
So the rules are simple... guess what's in the box in the tomb... that's it.
All you have to do is guess what's in the box on the tomb and that's it.
The losing team will be awarded the dreaded "no" point.
The losing team will be awarded the dreaded "no" points, one for each of you and three points for each of you.
The losing team will be awarded the dreaded "no-no" points.
Ueda-san, the writer
And I don't know if you've noticed, but I've accumulated 2 points.
I'm leading the ad-libbing, and I'm running in front of everyone, and I don't know why, but...
I don't know why.
Okay, let's do it.
Due to budget constraints, I can only put one hand in this time. I can only put one hand in this time due to budget constraints.
Please help us.
Not both hands, but only one hand.
I've never seen that before.
What did you say?
Amazon's lowest price.
Why? Because of the budget?
I have to answer.
Oh, you don't mind?
Go ahead, take a look, everyone.
Wow!
This is a little... This is bad!
This is amazing. Seriously, this is giving me goosebumps.
This might be a bad match.
What are you going to do?
Okay, Takanashi, let's go! 30 seconds, 30 seconds.
Takanashi's challenge!
Wow! I've never seen that before!
I've never seen that before! I've never seen that before! I've never seen anyone go that hard!
Okay, 10 seconds left.
Nine, five, four, three, two, one.
Takanashi is amazing. That's amazing.
Now for Fujisaki.
He might bite, so be careful. He'll bite!
He might bite for real, so be careful.
He might bite, so be careful.
He's my teammate.
LOL!LOL.
I forgot.
Here we go.
Fujisaki, yo, start!
Ai!
No, no, no, it's the box. It's an accident with the box. Go, go, go. Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Ah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
A-ha-ha-ha!
Come on!
Go, go, go, go!
A-ha-ha-ha!
Now, you have 10 seconds left.
Come on, 10 seconds.
Four.
Three, two, one.
That's it! Okay, cut it out, cut it out, cut it out.
Cut corners.
Now please go back.
But I think it was a great reaction.
Yeah, it's impossible.
That's good.
Now let's open all the answers at once!
Yes!
Cleaning brush.
For washing the bathtub and so on.
Wait a minute.
The... The.
Please write proper nouns more properly.
It's hard to tell.
What?
What do you mean?
It was in the school.
The brush that you use to clean the toilets.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, it feels the same.
Fujisaki, on the other hand...
The one for washing the bathtub.
Well, I only wash the bathtub.
I help out at home.
Oh?
When I wash the bathtub.
I see.
Well, let's see what you got right.
There it is!
Look! The bath washer!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
There's an official name for this thing... it's called a scrubbing brush.
But, well...
I'll take my chances.
I guess we're both right.
Yes! That's correct.
Now, let's take on the daily challenge of the elder sister's team
Here we go.
Don't look.
Don't look. Don't look.
Come on, you can do it.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, let's go.
I can go, I can go, I can go.
We're going.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ah!
Be careful
Be careful.
It's a lot lower. Be careful.
Watch out! Watch out!
Watch out!
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
All right, all right, all right, we're almost there.
Three, two, one, out!
You're surprisingly brave.
Come on, Sasaki, hang in there
Let's go, Sasaki! All right, let's go!Let's go, Sasaki! All right, let's go!
Watch out! Watch out!
Watch out! Slowly, slowly...
Watch out! Watch out! Watch out!
Finish it!
Look out! Look out!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
It stopped.
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Ten seconds left!
Yes!
Five, four, three, two, one!
That's it!
Now, let's see if you can write it down on the flip side.
Okay, OK!
Now, then, or open them all at once!
Pop!
Oh! Slime! Slime!
Okay, now, let's have a look.
Ready!
That's right! It's slime!
That's great!
What? You got it with just a little time to spare?
It was too easy!
It was easy!
You make it sound difficult.
It's this voice.
Okay, then,
Minamin?
Minamin.Minamin.
Se-ee, here you go!
Eeeeeeeeeee!
Come on, come on, the voltage is clearly higher than before.
They are easy-to-understand kids. They are easy-to-understand children.
Which way?
Eh, are you okay to touch it?
Oh, hey, is it okay to touch this?
What should I do?
Okay, now, let's do the shot.
Oh, no. Oh, are you sure it's okay to touch it or not?
Be careful.
Careful?
I think you should be careful.
That bad, huh?
What?
Okay, now, let's adjust the shot.
All right, let's go!
I'm scared.
First, the smell. There is no smell at all.
Oh, isn't this thing in there for 30 seconds already?
I was told so much.
Wow, scary. Wow!
Ugh, scary. Whoa!
A little lower, a little lower. A little lower, a little lower.
Still lower, still lower. Oh, no!
Still lower, still lower.
Santa, Santa, Santa. Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh.
Five, four, three, two, one, done.
Or that.Or.
Wet.
Wet is a lot wetter.
Smell, you can smell it.
Why, it stinks.
That's the worst smell I've ever smelled.
Why?
It stinks. What?
Come on, Nagamatsu.
Hang in there.
Let's go.
All right, let's go.
Come on, go for it.
Watch out.
Oh, no.
Laughter.
Laughing.
Watch out, it's going to get violent.
It's going to get violent.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
That's enough, that's enough, that's enough.
Here he comes.
He's gonna bite you, he's gonna bite you.
Don't touch the left side too much or he'll bite you.
It stinks.
I didn't smell it.
Three, two, one.
That's it.
Now, if you'll step back, please.
Wait a minute.Wait a minute.
Okay, then.
Please write it down.
Here's a hint: it's in season.
What's in season?
I've already got two choices.
Let's all flip it open at once!
Seino
Pacific saury, mackerel.
Come on.
Well, sure.
I don't know, so let's go with what's in season.
I see... saury.
Noon is mackerel.
Mackerel is in season?
Mackerel... well, it's in season around Bodybell.
It's so hot right now.
It's only hot right now.
It's hot right now.
Talk about the season.
All right, you two.
I need you both to line up next to each other at the same time.
I'm getting hit with this one.
Let's do this.
That's it!
The correct answer is "saury.
So, the high school team is one step ahead.
The high school team is one step ahead!
Yoshimura's challenge!
Here we go!All right, let's get started!
Ah!
Hey.
Go, go, go!
Down, down, down!
That's it!
Lower!
Hey, stop, stop, stop. It's not a bad idea.
Stop that!
A little more to the right!
Ten seconds left!
Come on!
He's up!
Three, two, one.
That's it!
He's up!
No, he's got courage!
Next, Takeru.
I'm so scared.
Takeru, I don't know if this is a good idea.
Here we go!
Here's Takeru's challenge. All right, let's go!
Left handed, left handed!
So fast!
Not even close!
Down! Down! Down!
Oh, no! Oh, no!Oh no! Oh no!
Go, go, go, go!
Go! Go!
Lower! Lower!
Giddyup!
Come on!
It's going down!
Four, three, two, one.
That's it!
I didn't touch anything!
What's that smell?
It's Mita Noodles.
Mita Seimen!
Amazing!
Yoshimura, this is quite an advantage.
What did I touch?
One more minute.
They're all open at once!
Go ahead!
Ready, go!
Yoshimura oden, bamboo shrimp dumplings
I could smell the fish at the counter of Mita Noodles.
Shrimp dumplings?
But they were round.
So they were dumplings?
I thought the round ones were eggs.
I don't know.I don't know.
Is it shrimp dumplings or oden?
I don't know.
Which is it? Okay, here we go.
Ready, set, go!
Wow!
That was great, Yoshimura!
Sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
It can't be shrimp dumplings!
Staff, you're so mean!
Shrimp balls! There's something that looks like a shrimp dumpling!
Shrimp balls!
I have to answer! I have to answer!
Okay, let's go! Ready, go!
Wow!
Can I touch this?
Can I touch this? I don't know.
Oh, man, this looks bad.
You did a good job.
Be really careful with this.
Oh, really?
If you go gaga over this, you might get hurt or something.
Really?
I'm serious. I'm afraid I'm gonna hurt myself.
Touch it slowly.
Okay, let's go.
Saito, come on!
Start it!
Be careful. Be careful.
Not quite there yet.
A little lower.
Not even close.
Saito!
I haven't touched anything, so still lower.
Still lower. Still lower.
Ten seconds left.
Saito, down.
Still down.
Go! Go! Go!
Five, four, three, two, one.
That's it.
Now Saito's touch is on the index finger.
Come on!
What's this?
That kind of game.
Guess what game.
What's this?
That kind of game
Okay, Natsume.
Go for it!
You can't lose
Let's go
Let's go!
Watch out, watch out!
Keep your hands to yourself!Don't spread out!
You'll get bit!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
He's gonna bite me!
Oh, no!
Watch out! Watch out!
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
Goo is better! Goo is better!
No, no, no, no, no! No, no, no, no!
No, no, no!
Ten seconds!
Oh, my God!
Three, two, one.
That's it!
Now then, write down what you think this is.
This is...
Oh! Natsume, you're pretty good with a pen.
I think I know what it is.
Oh!
Because Natsume touched it more often than me.
Now, the one who guesses correctly wins!
Now then, let's open all the flips at once!
Then!
What?
Well, well, well... once, Saito.
It feels like a daikon radish.
I see.
It was in a state, plus it was a little wet.It was in a state, plus it was a little wet.
I thought it was some kind of radish.
Moisture.
I see.
Okay, that's great. That's great.
That's nice.
Rika doll.
She had hair.
Um...
It had legs and a funny smell.
Excuse me, that Rika-chan doll.
That's vinyl.
It smells funny, so Rika-chan doll... like hair...
Okay, please get in line anyway.
I wonder what it is...
You'll regret it when you see it.
Regret?
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
The correct answer is shrimp!
The correct answer is shrimp! It's a shrimp! It was shrimp!
Okay, so...
Now, since both answers are incorrect
I'd like to move on to the Sudden Death Match.
Is there more?
He says there are more.
So, we'll select one.
Well, that's it, then, Mr. Representative.
Okay, what about the high school team?
I want to play, so I'll play.
Okay, Fujisaki, let's do it! Ok, let's go Fujisaki!
Against the team of the elder sister. Yes, with a bit of revenge.
Revenge! Let's go for revenge!
Let's go for it! Seriously, I don't think I've touched it the most.
You'll touch it next time, right? Next time, for sure.
I'm used to it. I'm used to it. I'll be fine.
Let's do Saito vs. Fujisaki.
Saito vs. Fujisaki.
Let's go, then, Saito. Let's do Saito's thing of touching already. Let's go for it.
Let's go, Saito. Let's go.
Let's go!
All right!
Ow! Ow! Oh, no!
Oh!
What the hell? I wonder why.
What's with the kelp? Oh, no! I can go!
Huh!
Whoa!
Go! Come on, come on, come on!
Go, go, go, go, go! Go, go, go, go!
Go for it!
Grab it!
Grab it! Grab it!
OK!
Aah!
Oh, my gosh!
Great leg angles!
Come on, there's still time!
Five!
Four!4!
3!
2!
One!
Yeah!
Whoo!
You got it?
I see something!
Something's coming out!
Fujisaki against Fujisaki!
I really wanted to see him win...
Go for it!
Let's go, Fujisaki!
Let's go!
Come on, oh, oh, oh, oh, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch! I've got it, I've got it, I've got it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, you're awesome! You can't touch me like that!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeah!
No mind! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Maybe you're playing a different game, Fujisaki. Cheers.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Mr. Fujisaki!
Here we go, three, two, one, done!
What? Huh?
Miku?
Miku? Miku?
Do you have the face of a murderer?
I don't have a face like that.
Okay, let's flip it.
It doesn't have to be a business card like this.It doesn't have to be a business card like this.
Oh no, Fujisaki's already in the pen.
Wait a minute. Oh no!
So this is where it's going to end.
It's done.
Hold on a second.
Excuse me.
Riasai, hait.
What? What is it?
Oh, my God.
What is it?
You're hysterical.
Hysterical.
I got suckered into that audition.
You're so fucking funny.
I didn't know you were that guy. We're...
It's so funny.
But, but, but, each one of us is probably...
We're slowly, slowly getting into character.
It's funny. That's what I'm talking about.
Okay, okay, you got it, you got it, you got it.
Okay, open all the answers at once.
There you go!
Okay, first of all, Saito.
What?
Jelly on a tube
Oh, jelly on a tube.
Yes, sir.
I see. I see.
Oh, tubular.
Oh, no, it's not.
Uh, well, it's, uh, it's a state of...
Oh, I'm sorry, no.
Silly girl.
Jelly on a tube
Looks like Ghibli.
That's good.
Jelly on a tube, good.
Totally fine.
It's good if Hayao retires.
When you retire.
Tubular jelly, what kind of occasion is this for?
In the summer, when you send it to your relatives.
Oh, the year-end gift type?
Jelly for the end of the year.
Jelly for year-end gifts.
The eating kind.
Eating jelly.
The expensive kind.
Yes, sir.
Okay, yes.
Fujisaki, the kind you put on your forehead when you get a fever, soak it in water and inflate it.
Oh.
You got it.
That's it.I'm totally over it.
Miku calls it "hot-pegging" at home.
Well, it varies from region to region.
When you put it in water, it expands, like this flattened part.
That's what I thought.
I've done it before.
I've done it before, watching YouTube.
Oh, I see.
Okay, let's go to the two of you.
All together, let's do it!
Let's do it!
So, the correct answer is...
Chilled peta, the kind you put on your head and inflate it.
Fujisaki got it right!
Yes!
That's wonderful!
Wonderful!
Wonderful.
Fujisaki, he's scared.
Fujisaki, you're scaring me.
He's too scared to be happy.
Next, thanks to Fujisaki!
So, the winners, the high school team!
That was close, by one point.
Well, that was close. It's Sudden, so I've got something for you.
Fujisaki was very dexterous, and he answered both questions correctly.
So, the losing team will get one no point each.
So, Takanashi now has 2 points.
Does that mean we're in line now?You mean you just got in line?
Yes, I just got in line.
No, I mean, it was crazy good.
It was fun. It was crazy.
People had great reactions.
Thank you so much for watching.
Today, we're going to have a conversation on WINK
Let me shout, let me cry
Even if I cry
You make me like you, like you, like you
Remember more and more is not so
I'm looking forward to working with you